A Guide to the Population Council records, Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) 1969-1971 Project Files, Accession 2, RG 2, Series 11 FA1431
Rockefeller Archive Center
- New York Medical College (NYMC) - A.4 - Reports - Program Progress (Box 24, Folder 233)
- New York Medical College (NYMC) - A.5. - Payments and Financial Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 234)
- Temple University - B.1. - Correspondence - General, 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 235)
- Temple University - B.2. - Proposal Program Period B, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 236)
- Temple University - B.3. - Contract Amendment Program Period B, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 237)
- Temple University - B.4.a. - Reports - Program Progress (Box 25, Folder 238)
- Temple University - B.5.a. - Financial - Provisional Reports, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 239)
- Temple University - B.5.b. - Financial - Final Reports, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 240)
- Temple University - B.6. - Audit Period B, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 241)
- Temple University - A.1. - Correspondence - General, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 242)
- Temple University - A.2. - Proposal Year A (Box 25, Folder 243)
- Temple University - A.3. - Agreement Year A, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 244)
- Temple University - A.4 - Reports - Program Progress, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 245)
- Temple University - A.5. - Payments and Financial Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 25, Folder 246)
- University of Chicago - B.1. - Correspondence - General, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 247)
- University of Chicago - B.2. - Proposal Program Period B, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 248)
- University of Chicago - B.3. - Contract Amendment Program Period B, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 249)
- University of Chicago - B.4.a. - Reports - Program Progress, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 250)
- University of Chicago - B.4.b. - Reports - Site Visits, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 251)
- University of Chicago - B.5.b. - Financial - Final Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 252)
- University of Chicago - B.5.c. - Financial - Payments, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 253)
- University of Chicago - A.1. - Correspondence - General, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 254)
- University of Chicago - A.2. - Proposal Year A, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 255)
- University of Chicago - A.3. - Agreement Year A, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 256)
- University of Chicago - A.4 - Reports - Program Progress, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 257)
- University of Chicago - A.5. - Payments and Financial Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 258)
- University of Florida - B.1. - Correspondence - General, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 258A)
- University of Florida - B.2. - Proposal Program Period B, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 259)
- University of Florida - B.3. - Contract Amendment Program Period B (Box 26, Folder 260)
- University of Florida - B.4.a. - Reports - Program Progress (Box 26, Folder 261)
- University of Florida - B.4.b. - Reports - Site Visits, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 262)
- University of Florida - B.5.a. - Financial - Provisional Reports (Box 26, Folder 263)
- University of Florida - B.5.b. - Financial - Final Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 264)
- University of Florida - B.5.c. - Financial - Payments, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 265)
- University of Florida - B.6 - Audit - Period B, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 266)
- University of Florida - A.1. - Correspondence - General, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 267)
- University of Florida - A.2. - Proposal Year A (Box 26, Folder 268)
- University of Florida - A.3. - Agreement Year A, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 269)
- University of Florida - A.4 - Reports - Program Progress, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 270)
- University of Florida - A.5. - Payments and Financial Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 271)
- Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) - Evaluation, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 272)
- Forms (Box 27, Folder 273)
- Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) Medical Schools - Agreements with Sub-Grantees, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 274)
- Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) Medical Schools - Financial Statements, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 275)
- 69.101 - Case Western Reserve University - Year 1 and Year 2 Grant Requests (Box 27, Folder 276)
- Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) - Budget Revisions (Box 27, Folder 277)
- 69.104 - International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - Year 1 and Year 2 Grant Requests (Box 27, Folder 278)
- 69.105 - Johns Hopkins - Year 1 and Year 2 Grant Requests (Box 27, Folder 279)
- 69.108 - University of Chicago - Year 1 and Year 2 Grant Requests (Box 27, Folder 280)
- 69.109 - University of Florida - Year 1 and Year 2 Grant Requests (Box 27, Folder 281)
- 69.110 - University of Pennsylvania - Year 1 and Year 2 Grant Requests (Box 27, Folder 282)
- 69.111 - University of Pittsburgh - Magee Women's Hospital - Year 1 and Year 2 Grant Requests (Box 28, Folder 283)
- 69.112 - Wayne State - Year 1 and Year 2 Grant Requests (Box 28, Folder 284)
- Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) Medical Schools - Proposal Year 2, Population Council Proposal (Box 28, Folder 285)
- 69.102 - Columbia - Harlem Hospital - Year 1 and Year 2 Grant Requests (Box 28, Folder 286)
- 69.106 - New York Medical College - Year 1 and Year 2 Grant Requests (Box 28, Folder 287)
- 69.107 - Temple University - Year 1 and Year 2 Grant Requests (Box 28, Folder 288)
- 69.100 - Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Year 1 and Year 2 Grant Requests (Box 28, Folder 289)
- 69.103 - Emory University - Year 1 and Year 2 Grant Requests (Box 28, Folder 290)
- Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) Medical Schools - Budgets (Box 28, Folder 291-292)